Guide to the Honors Theses 1989-2008 [Call #]
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
Honors Theses1989-2008
[Call #]
9.5 linear feet (12 boxes)
Eastern Connecticut State University
The Honors Theses Collection includes original documents created by senior students in the Honors Program. The theses cover a broad range of subject areas and represent most academic departments. New theses are added at the end of the spring semester each year.
Provenance
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers with some restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Honors Theses Collection includes original documents created by senior students in the Honors Program. Theses in Series I, II & III were given to the archives in 2005 by Professor Philip Elliot, Head of the Honors Program. This original group of theses is dated 1989-2002. The theses cover a broad range of subject areas and represent most academic departments. Most theses include a cover page with dates of review, the names of the reader/reviewer(s) and the name of the student advisor. This is an open collection. New theses are added at the end of the spring semester each year.
Scope and Content Note
Series I - 1989-1994 - This series includes 23 theses representing a variety of topics including: biology, sociology, environmental earth science, history, communications, mathematics, economics and psychology.
Series II - 1995-1999 - This series includes 56 theses representing a variety of topics including: biology, history, mathematics & computer science, visual arts, English, communications, education, gender, business and political science.
Series III - 2000-2004 - This series includes 70 theses representing a variety of topics in the fields of education, biology, medicine, technology, health, psychology, communications, publishing, business, history, mathematics & computer science, philosophy, performing arts, gender, environmental studies, geography, literature and political science.
Series IV - 2005-2009 - This series currently includes [63] theses representing a variety of topics in the fields of communications, psychology, sociology, history, political science, athletics, visual art, literature, creative writing, medicine, biology, physical science, statistics, economics, mathematics and business.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged chronologically.
The files are grouped into series:
Series I - 1989-1994
Series II - 1995-1999
Series III - 2000-2004
Series IV - 2005-2009
Access Points
Subject Organizations:
Eastern Connecticut State University.
Subject Topics:
Universities and colleges -- Students.
Document Types:
Unpublished manuscripts.; Audio-visuals.; Photographs.
Other Names:
[OTHER NAMES]
Container List
[The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.]
- Series I - 1989-1994
  - Cunningham, Kaye Avarann St. Claire The Medicinal Use and Ecology of Two Epiphytic…, 1989 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Meskony, Donna A. Hormonal, Immunologic, and Metabolic Effects of…, May 1990 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Noel, Dawn E. Methodologies for Community Needs Assessments, 1991 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Darby, Nichola E. Environmental Marketing and the Average High…, May 1992 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Bowen, Barbara J. Patterns of Malarial Infection in North American…., 1993 (Box 1a, Item 1)
  - Bradanini, Sherry K., Fractal World, 1993 (Box 1a, Item 5)
  - Corn, Aqualina A Study of the Effect of Seasonal and Spatial Variation..., 1993 (Box 1a, Item 6)
  - Curtis, Stephen Delocalization at WILI: The Changes…., Apr 1993 (Box 1a, Item 7)
  - Dziurgot, Vicki Connecticut’s Forgotten Workers: Women in the New…, Apr 1993 (Box 1a, Item 8)
  - Ernst, Wendy The Effect of Host Density and Sixe, Leaf …, 1993 (Box 1a, Item 9)
  - Freeman, Marc The Heat Shock Response of Chlamydomonas…, 1993 (Box 1a, Item 10)
  - Gregorio, Joseph Bootstrapping for the Correlation Coefficient, [1993] (Box 1a, Item 11)
  - Griffin, Wayne Transitions From Planned To Market Economics…, 1993 (Box 1a, Item 12)
  - Memmott. Jr., Richard C. Eastern’s Hero 1 Robot (1 of 2), Mar 1993 (Box 1a, Item 13)
  - Memmott. Jr., Richard C. (2 of 2), Mar 1993 (Box 1a, Item 14)
  - Battaglia, Maria The Evolutionary Ecology of North American…, 1994 (Box 1a, Item 15)
  - Cartier, Dawn C. Gender Bias in Mathematical Textbooks, Mar 1994 (Box 1a, Item 16)
  - Jensen, Solvej R. The Amateur Videographer, 1994 (Box 1a, Item 17)
  - Levesque, Nicole Elaine New Trends in the Male Female Wage-Gap….., Mar 1994 (Box 1a, Item 18)
  - Montie, Melissa M. The Individualized Bilingual Pacing Program for Math (1 of 2), May 1994 (Box 1a, Item 19)
  - Montie, Melissa M. (2 of 2), May 1994 (Box 1a, Item 20)
  - Perera, Dilani Cross-Cultural Differences in Depression, 1994 (Box 1a, Item 21)
  - Urban, Betty G. Nontraditional Students: barriers and Motivating…, May 1994 (Box 1a, Item 22)
- Series II - 1995-1999
  - Bernegger, Joshua N. “Abuse of the Emergency Medical Services (1 of 2), Apr 1995 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Bernegger, Joshua N. (2 of 2), Apr 1995 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Boucher, Michelle The Rebirth of Athena: Female Mentorship in…., [1995] (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Lemieux, Nichole The Ever-Changing Algebraic Word Problem, 1995 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Marocchini, Debby ‘English Cretors’ and Native Americans in Southern…, Apr 1995 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Mattei, Isis Rakia Women of Color Artists: Slide Registry, May 1995 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - O’Meara, Jodie Animal Transformations in the Brothers Grimm…., 1995 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Jones, Janice L. Pathways to Self-Sufficiency AFDC: Problems…, Mar 1996 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Jones, Janice L. (2 of 2), Mar 1996 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Magnuson, Kristen A Study of the Metabolic Profile of the Locomotor…, May 1996 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Pettengill, Matthew Jay A Comparative Histochemical Analysis…, May 1996 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Schaible, Stacy Managerial Decision Making and Ethical Referents, [1996] (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Abert, Michele Is the Diagnostic Label Beneficial or Detrimental for..., 1997 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Bennett III, Wallace O. Does Pressure Induce the Production of Heat Shock…, May 1997 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Bopko, Amy Open Adoption in Connecticut, Apr 1997 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Conkling, Jennifer Interpersonal Realtionships and the Internet: A Look…, May 1997 (Box 2, Item 16)
  - Croteau, Jason T. Interspecific and Intraspecific Variation in Plasma…., [1997] (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Dolye, Dennis The Humanitarian Impulse: The Hartford Retreat for …., Apr 1997 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - Dolye, Dennis (2 of 2), Apr 1997 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - Heisler, Judith A. The Implementation and Effectiveness of …., Mar 1997 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Holt, Jeffrey Both heatshock and deflagellation result in the…., May 1997 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Johnson, Michael P. A Histochemical and Ultrastructural Comparison of…., May 1997 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Lawrence, Timothy Correlation between Aspects of Parental Care and…., May 1997 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Lemons, Karen A. Investigation into the Function of HSP7- During…., May 1997 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - McLean, April A. An analysis of a Serial Killer, [1997] (Box 3, Item 6)
  - Reutter, Nathan A Study of Fecal Coliform Density Upstream…., Dec 1997 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - Sperrazza, Lisa A. Child Abuse and the Media: A Content Analysis of…., Apr 1997 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Sperrazza, Lisa A. (2 of 2), Apr 1997 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - Walpole, Emily Poetry and Politics and the Work of Adrienne Rich, [1997] (Box 3, Item 10)
  - Barwuah, Yaw The Role of Nutritional Requirement in the Growth…, Apr 1998 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - Caouette, Becky Mine and Yours, Yours and Mine: Acknowledge and…, Mar 1998 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - Gervais, Tracy A Histochemical Analysis of the Third and Fifth Leg…, May 1998 (Box 3, Item 13)
  - Larson, Jessica D. Is Flagellar Component Pool Size Related to Flagellar…, May 1998 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - Maniscalco, Amanda M. Communication Software in Early Childhood Special…, Apr 1998 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - Mudgett, Kelly Attacking the Archetype: Feminist Revisions…., Mar 1998 (Box 3, Item 16)
  - Rodrigue, Vicky How many Hsp70s are there in Chlamydomonas…, Apr 1998 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - Shadish, Melanie Cardiovascular Adaptations to Exercise in the Blue…, May 1998 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Sokolowska, Elzbieta The Influence of the Mass Media on Public Opinion…, May 1998 (Box 3, Item 19)
  - Wenzel, Beth The Effects of Habitat Defoliation on the Reproduction.., May 1998 (Box 3, Item 20)
  - Zasso, Robert Significance of the West Louisiana Campaign…, May 1998 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - Caldeira, Stacey The Use of Peers in the Social Skills Training of…., Apr 1999 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - Comstock, Sarah G. Homeless Children: The Effects of Homelessness on…., May 1999 (Box 4, Item 2)
  - Fischer, Kateri A. Immunological Evidence for the Chaperone Func…., May 1999 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - Godden, Richard H. The Function of Egeus in Chaucer’s: The Knight’s Tale, [1999] (Box 4, Item 4)
  - Krok, Mariah From Paradise Lost to Paradise Now: An Exploration…, May 1999 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - Leahey, Patricia The Influence of the Rhetoric of Democratic Theory…, 1999 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - McDermott, Anne M. Organosilicone Surfactants as Potential Miticides, May 1999 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - Milikin, Mark Surficial Geology and Fluid Transport in the ECSU…, May 1999 (Box 4, Item 8)
  - Milikin, Mark (2 of 2), May 1999 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - Negron, Yolanda Cuba and Puerto Rico, Mar 1999 (Box 4, Item 10)
  - Riquier, Carol Anne Children’s Television Advertising and Gender, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Item 11)
  - Samela, Sara An Informational Campaign for the Center for Conn…., Oct 1999 (Box 4, Item 12)
  - Samela, Sara (2 of 2), Oct 1999 (Box 4, Item 13)
  - Seeley, E. Scott Molecular Cloning of Chlamydomonas Kinesin II…, 1999 (Box 4, Item 14)
  - Wade, Katherine Do Magazine Advertisements Have a Negative…., 1999 (Box 4, Item 15)
  - Wasilewski, Heather Women’s Burden: A Study of Victorian mourning…, [1999] (Box 4, Item 16)
  - Wasilewski, Heather (2 of 2), [1999] (Box 4, Item 17)
  - Zengou, Ryan A. Age-Related Changes in Integrin-Mediated Cell…., May 1999 (Box 4, Item 18)
- Series III - 2000-2004
  - Ashton, Kimberly The Gender Earning Gap, 2000 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Blair, Sarah Ann Manganese Toxicity in Human Fibroblast Cells, May 2000 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - Blankert, JennieMarie Examining the Factors which Lead to Successful …., Apr 2000 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - Campisi, Denise N. The Effect of Corticosterone Treatment on the…., May 2000 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - Canniff, Kara The Development of Fluency with and without Errors, [2000] (Box 5, Item 5)
  - Canniff, Kara (2 of 2), [2000] (Box 5, Item 6)
  - Dodds, Janette How Do Peer Relationships Develop among…, 2000 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - Fried, Heather A. An Investigation of Observed Morphological…., Apr 2000 (Box 5, Item 8)
  - Heft, Todd The Effects of Computers on the Social Behavior of…, May 2000 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - Johnson, Aimee The Influence on Moral Reasoning in Children, May 2000 (Box 5, Item 10)
  - Kupfer, Christina Sex and Power: The Relationship among Environment… (1 of 2), [2000] (Box 5, Item 11)
  - Kupfer, Christina (2 of 2), [2000] (Box 5, Item 12)
  - Lefevre, Jennifer M. The New Millennium and the Transformation of …., Mar 2000 (Box 5, Item 13)
  - Rivers, Nathan A Comparison of ADALINE and Backpropagation…, May 2000 (Box 5, Item 14)
  - Schmidt, Catherine Characterization of Myosin Isoforms in Depressor…, 2000 (Box 5, Item 15)
  - Stearns, Sarah An Investigation of Cardiovascular Adaptations to…, May 2000 (Box 5, Item 16)
  - Stoker, Amber Human Rights and the Illegal Immigrant…., 2000 (Box 5, Item 17)
  - Voorheis, Kathleen E. Make it Count: Eastern Connecticut State University…., May 2000 (Box 5, Item 18)
  - Watcke, Jennifer L. Merger Trends (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 5, Item 19)
  - Watcke, Jennifer L. (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 5, Item 20)
  - Baumgartner, Lisa Entomopatogenic Nematodes: The Effect of ….., Apr 2001 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock Altruism and the State, Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (2 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 3)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (3 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 4)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (4 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 5)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (5 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 6)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (6 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 7)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (7 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 8)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (8 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 9)
  - Chapdelaine, John Babcock (9 of 9), Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 10)
  - Dickman, Kathryn Direct Observation of ADHD Children and Their…., [2001] (Box 6, Item 11)
  - Firlik, Julie The Impact of Immigration on a Nation’s Economy, May 2001 (Box 6, Item 12)
  - Heinonen, Kari Foraging Behavior of an Invasive Crab, Hemigrapsus…., May 2001 (Box 6, Item 13)
  - Heller, Sandra J. Curbstone Press (Video), [2001] (Box 6, Item 14)
  - Mandes, Holly Are Easy-to-Read Books Quality Literature?...., Mar 2001 (Box 6, Item 15)
  - Martin, Misty Rae The Efficacy of Praise and Teachers’ Use of It In…, [2001] (Box 6, Item 16)
  - Mbonye, Uri R. Quantitative Analysis of Pyramidal Neurons and Beta…, May 2001 (Box 6, Item 17)
  - Murphy, Mike Street Fighting Women: Women in the Radical…., Apr 2001 (Box 6, Item 18)
  - Olcott, Mandy The Role of Integrins in the Senescence of Human…., [2002] (Box 6, Item 19)
  - Thomson, Beth Animals in the Children’s Literature of Latin America…, May 2001 (Box 6, Item 20)
  - Bartlett, Angela Beyond Money: Motivating Younger Generations, Mar 2002 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Feder, Luke Dismantling the Natural Aristocracy: The Rhetoric…., May 2002 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - Fetta, Fiorigio The Style of Techno Music (Video), May 2002 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - Green, Karen Formula For Success, May 2002 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - Green, Karen (2 of 2), May 2002 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Keleher, Rebecca The Use of Complex Numbers in Geometric Proof, Dec 2002 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - Martin, Misty Rae The Efficacy of Praise and Teachers’ Use of it in the…, 2002 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Seaman, Nina A Study of Forgotten People: The Homeless in…., 2002 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Thomson, Beth Animals in the Children’s Literature of Latin America., May 2001 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - Twomey, Erin The Uses and Gratifications of Radio in the 21st…., Mar 2002 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - Waters, Michelle The Effects of Fluency of Component Skills on…., 2002 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - Waters, Michelle (2 of 2), [2002] (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Wetherell, Michael Bedrock Geology of the South Section of the …, [2002] (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Beaulieu, Kristie Lynn Modeling Terrain in GIs, May 2003 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Beechwood, Justin Contemporary Issues Concerning the Future of Analog…, 2003 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - Champagne, Bethany The Relationship between Amount of Sleep and….., 2003 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - Collins, Laura E. Assessment of Apoptosis in Pyramidal Neurons in…., May 2003 (Box 8, Item 4)
  - Corneau, Keri “A Guide to Stage Managing: A discussion of the roles… (1 of 2), May 2003 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - Corneau, Keri (2 of 2), May 2003 (Box 8, Item 6)
  - Cote, John On Decimal Expansions of Rational Numbers, May 2003 (Box 8, Item 7)
  - Desjardins, Karla Do Negative Cinematic Images of the Death Penalty…, 2003 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - DuBois, Laura Web Wonders: A Study in What Element Create the…., 2003 (Box 8, Item 9)
  - DuBois, Susan Women Entering Technology, 2003 (Box 8, Item 10)
  - Monsonis, Danielle The Parallel World of Narnia: How C.S. Lewis…, May 2003 (Box 8, Item 11)
  - Poirier, Melissa A. Using objects of Obsession as Tokens: A Follow…, 2003 (Box 8, Item 12)
  - Stevens, Ashley A Study of Essenism and Significant Parallels to…., Mar 2003 (Box 8, Item 13)
  - Testori, Peter Anthony Motherhood and the Quest for Identity in Literature…, May 2003 (Box 8, Item 14)
  - Tourtellotte, Sara, Dec 2003 (Box 8, Item 15)
  - White, Joanna The Influence of Yoga on the Quality of Life…., 2003 (Box 8, Item 16)
  - ZuWallack, Alaine F. Determination of antibacterial Sensitivity of newly…., May 2003 (Box 8, Item 17)
  - Fitzgerald, Brian Cognitive Development and the Importance of…., Jun 2004 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - Heyanka, Dan Assessment of Self-Esteem as a Result of Sports…., May 2004 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - Hornung, Jessica How Far Can You Go? Measuring 802.2lb Wireless…., Mar 2004 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Karki, Roshan Identification of Flagellar Proteins in Chlamydomonas.., Oct 2004 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - Klar, Melissa Anne School Vouchers: Individual Opinions based on…. (1 of 2), May 2004 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - Klar, Melissa Anne (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - Parness, Todd Effects of Player Anxiety on The Home Field…., May 2004 (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Pion, Kerri (1 of 5) An Analysis of Middle Grade Student Opinion…., May 2004 (Box 9, Item 8)
  - Pion, Kerri (2 of 5 Appendix A), May 2004 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - Pion, Kerri (3 of 5 Appendix B), May 2004 (Box 9, Item 10)
  - Pion, Kerri (4 of 5 Appendix C), May 2004 (Box 9, Item 11)
  - Pion, Kerri (5 of 5 Appendix D), May 2004 (Box 9, Item 12)
  - Schofield, Stacey Lynn The Cost of Competition: The Female Athlete Triad…, Mar 2004 (Box 9, Item 13)
  - Scialla, Marlena Fun with Inverses modulo n, May 2004 (Box 9, Item 14)
  - Shojaiyan, Poyan A Quantitative Study of Ubiquitin, Senile Plaques…., May 2004 (Box 9, Item 15)
  - Stankoski, Raymond M. A Rhetorical Analysis of the Arguments for….., Mar 2004 (Box 9, Item 16)
  - Strout, Danielle The Biological Etiology of Austin, May 2004 (Box 9, Item 17)
  - Vachon, Danielle Bilingualism within American Schools, May 2004 (Box 9, Item 18)
  - Zizik, Kristina Where the Water runs: A Call for Uniform National…., Apr 2004 (Box 9, Item 19)
- Series IV - 2005-2009
  - Bernier, Amity Effects of Parental Exposure to Marijuana, Mar 2005 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Bonetti, Anthony The Construction of Gender Through The Use…, Mar 2005 (Box 10, Item 2)
  - Gilbride, Amy Hope Fades: A Creative Honors Thesis, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 3)
  - Murdock, Nicholas O. The Effect of Social Environment on Foraging…., May 2005 (Box 10, Item 4)
  - Nass, Brian British and American Reaction in the Media…, Apr 2005 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - Nielson, Erik The Making of a Monster: William Godwin’s…., Apr 2005 (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Ostrove, William, N. Eduard Bernstein and Rosa Luxemburg, Economucs…, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 7)
  - Piro, Justin R. HU Binding to Discontinuous DNA Oligonucleotides, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 8)
  - Proniewych, Lauren The Influence of a Strength Training Program…, Apr 2005 (Box 10, Item 9)
  - Rodriguez, Robyn The Allied Strategic Bombing Campaign Against…, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 10)
  - Roehl, Molly The Victorian Feminine Ideal in Kate Chopin’s…., May 2005 (Box 10, Item 11)
  - Schneider, Rebecca C. Media Influence on the Democratic Presidential…., May 2005 (Box 10, Item 12)
  - Smith, Majessire L. Gender Differences in Reaction to Infidelity, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 13)
  - Smith, Sara Nation- Building: Lessons Learned From Bosnia…, May 2005 (Box 10, Item 14)
  - Traver, Brenna The Efficacy of Natural Dyes as Light Activates…., Dec 2005 (Box 10, Item 15)
  - Burchard, Grace The Wall, Mar 2006 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Dains, Krystal A Fellowship in the Making, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - Fearon, Megan Enzyme Kinetics: Modeling the Reaction Rate of…., May 2006 (Box 11, Item 3)
  - Fitzgerald, Matthew Adolescents and Relationship a Collection of short…., May 2006 (Box 11, Item 4)
  - Hotkowski, Mary P. The Life of Purpose:Narration and Alcott’s…., May 2006 (Box 11, Item 5)
  - Impelluso, Kaitlin. The Influence of Media on Different Aged…, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 6)
  - Kehoegreen, Meaghan A New England Industrial Town versus…., May 2006 (Box 11, Item 7)
  - Kline, Katherine Britain’s Movement towards Europe…, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 8)
  - McPhee, Jenninfer Women in Bridgeport Factories: World War I, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 9)
  - Sarfati, Ami Writing a Play: A Gay Man in Wonderland, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 10)
  - Schneider, Sara A Jack of All Trades: The Historical Truth and…, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 11)
  - Segura, Carl, Anxiety I college Student- Athletes and Non…, May 2006 (Box 11, Item 12)
  - Whitehead, Brian Chains of Circles Tangent to Two Other Circles…, Apr 2006 (Box 11, Item 13)
  - Barrett, Heather Internal Branding and Emotional Dissonance in…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 1)
  - Bogue, Rachel L. Cultural Revolution and its effect on women’s…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 2)
  - Borkowski, Krista Money Supply and Inflation: Determining…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - Devine, Colleen C. Cholesterol Knowledge and Dietary Behaviors…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - Gaudioso, Tom Emergency Action Awareness at college…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 5)
  - Hileman, Sarah A Comprehensive Investigation of William…., Jan 2007 (Box 12, Item 6)
  - Jacobson, Brian The DeNazification of the Ivory Tower…., May 2007 (Box 12, Item 7)
  - Kramer, Michelle The Impact of the Modern Civil Rights Struggle…., May 2007 (Box 12, Item 8)
  - Lennon, Carter A. Body Image: Does your Awareness Affect Your…., May 2007 (Box 12, Item 9)
  - Lincoln, James William Mythology and Fiction as means to Truth; the…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 10)
  - Mangles, Allison Martin Luther King and the Poor People’s Campaign…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 11)
  - Monroe, Amber L. The Female Captivity Narrative 1670-1900, Apr 2007 (Box 12, Item 12)
  - Piro, Andrew Waiting for life to hit: A Creative Writing Project…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 13)
  - Rigatti, Marc Isolation of Antimicrobial Molecules From…, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 14)
  - Schlask, Jessica M. When Morning Comes: A Novella, May 2007 (Box 12, Item 15)
  - Swanson, Lindsay Important Decision to Minimize Loss Related…, Apr 2007 (Box 12, Item 16)
  - Sweet, Matthew Slaughter House Five: Deconstructing the…, Apr 2007 (Box 12, Item 17)
  - White, David M. Motivation, Means, and Execution in Connecticut..., May 2007 (Box 12, Item 18)
  - Altier, Heather R. Gender and Perspective Regarding Infidelity, Jan 2008 (Box 12, Item 19)
  - Bomster, Hailie Jo Abraham Lincoln: How His Importance Grew, 2008 (Box 12, Item 20)
  - Braboy, Fannie R.J. Alzheimer’s Disease and Neurofibrillary…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 21)
  - Carlo, Rosanne A Dramatistic and Role Analysis: Case Study…, Apr 2008 (Box 12, Item 22)
  - Clampett, Megan Lorraine Everything Was Beautiful: A Collection of…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 23)
  - Cornell, Kimberly E. Parasocial Relationships, Jan 2008 (Box 12, Item 24)
  - Cuttler, Courtney Portraiture Post-Photography: An Investigation…, Apr 2008 (Box 12, Item 25)
  - Harrington, Erika Perceived Reciam as a Predictor of Depression…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 26)
  - Jassil, Ryan Motivation to Learn, Goal Orientation…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 27)
  - LaFlamme, Jenna Going up in Flames: Heretical Literature of the…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 28)
  - Lombardozzi, Dominick M. Understanding Factor Analysis and its Application…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 29)
  - Matteau, Tyler A. Superman and the Mad Psychiatrist: How Censorship…, May 2008 (Box 12, Item 30)
  - Morris, Stephanie The Mathematics behind Graduation and Its App….., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 31)
  - Plantamura, Allison M. Contribution to Wage Difference of Recent College…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 32)
  - Spreda, Kimberly The Natural Pacifist: Three British Feminist….., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 33)
  - Whitehead, Gregory Intangible Assets and Cell Phone Company…., May 2008 (Box 12, Item 34)
  - York, Sarah Determinants of Mothers’ Labor Force Attachment, May 2008 (Box 12, Item 35)